<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-06-08T00:05:27+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Lilly Session 2</title><link href="/2020/06/07/lilly-session-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lilly Session 2" /><published>2020-06-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-06-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2020/06/07/lilly-session-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/06/07/lilly-session-2.html">&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Research answers
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Who is my audience?&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Who are the decision makers (principals, parents, teachers)?
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;what is their budget&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Who are my competitors?
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;What are other different programs, people that are offering something&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;What do customers potentially pay (competitive analysis)&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;How much money do I want to make? What are my living costs? What are my other jobs?
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;My goal by the end of 2020 is to get ……&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Build over time?&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;How many tiny towns can I facilitate at once? How much time do I want to work on this?
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Nanny share - get 6 parents together&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;ECE share&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;And we’re going to learn
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Ask parents of Tiny Towners
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;survey?&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I want to hire people? (later)
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Business partner - do I want to worry about it&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Find an investor - go to wealthy uncle, here’s my 4 year plan, and you’ll get an x-return on it&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Go to the bank, get a business loan, I need a business loan, this is what I need (their interest rates suck)&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Write an adjacent contract
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Calculate how much it costs, how much i want to be paid for this offering&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;what other assumptions do I have that I can test out in the second term&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;non-compete
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;I’m looking to position this as an offering to parent groups, other schools&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;what do you think is the value is as a parent?&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;how would this positioning be read by you? would you be interested?&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;if you can’t pay me, here’s what I need:&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;happy to do it for another semester, super appreciative for the stage and container in which I develop it&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Research answers Who is my audience? Who are the decision makers (principals, parents, teachers)? what is their budget Who are my competitors? What are other different programs, people that are offering something What do customers potentially pay (competitive analysis) How much money do I want to make? What are my living costs? What are my other jobs? My goal by the end of 2020 is to get …… Build over time? How many tiny towns can I facilitate at once? How much time do I want to work on this? Nanny share - get 6 parents together ECE share And we’re going to learn</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tiny Town Debrief Questions</title><link href="/2020/06/06/tiny-town-debrief-questions.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tiny Town Debrief Questions" /><published>2020-06-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-06-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2020/06/06/tiny-town-debrief-questions</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/06/06/tiny-town-debrief-questions.html">&lt;p&gt;Ayako: &lt;img src=&quot;../../../assets/images/2020-06-06-ayako-advice.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
Kay: &lt;img src=&quot;../../../assets/images/2020-06-06-questions.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Ayako:</summary></entry></feed>